seoclarity.net 2019-11-19

# Privacy Policy - seoClarity

  1. Introduction.
  2. Information we collect.
  3. How do we use your information?
  4. Retention of personal information.
  5. How we share information we collect?
  6. Transfer of information internationally.
  7. Technology we use.
  8. Access, update and delete your personal data.
  9. Contact our Data Privacy Officer (DPO).

### **1\. Introduction.**

At Actonia, we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy applies to our website www.seoclarity.net and our Search Engine Optimization management platform seoClarity. This policy explains how Actonia collects, uses and protects your Information, including data that is personal to you and can identify you an as individual. It also describes how you can access, update and delete your personal information.

We will post any privacy policy changes to this page. Additionally, we may provide notice of prominent updates by sending you an email or if you are a user of our platform, via a notification through the app.

Prior to using our services, please read this policy completely so there is full clarity on your relationship with us.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our use of the information you provide us, please email us at [privacy@seoclarity.net](mailto:privacy@seoclarity.net) or by mail to:

Attn: Privacy  
seoClarity  
9701 W. Higgins Rd Ste. 320   
Rosemont, IL 60018

### **2\. Information we collect.**

We collect information that you provide to us directly, such as username, name, address, email, phone number as well as other information that could be used to identify you.

We may also gather credit card/other payment information, if that is provided to us during payment of a contract or for services rendered.

We also gather technical data automatically about your computer or devices and their location, ip address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, site interaction data, date/time stamp, clickstream data, etc using a variety of technologies including but not limited to cookies, flash cookies, pixels, web beacons, logs and other technologies.

Information about you may also be gathered from other sources such as third party sites, social networking sites. Contact information, search term and search result information may also be procured from business information database providers.

We send push notifications from time to time to update you about feature updates, events or promotions both via email and via notification on our platform.

We may link information we store within our analytics software to Personal Information you submit within our platform or on our website.

Our website and platform are not intended for or targeted at children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 13 years of age. If you have feel that we have gathered data for any child under 13, please contact us at privacy@seoclarity.net so we may take immediate corrective action.

### **3\. How do we use your information?**

Our use of your personal information depends on your relationship with us.

Typically your personal data is used in the following manner:

Provision of services in accordance with the contractual obligations to you or your company.

In order to comply with legal obligations such as financial reporting, court orders, warrants, etc in accordance with applicable law.

To communicate with you about our services, promotions, newsletters, SEO and content marketing news and updates, and special offers or private updates about new features and products.

With any forms submitted on our site, you consent to allow seoClarity to store and process this personal information you provided to contact you about the content you requested. 

For maintaining and improving our site and platform. We may also use your IP addresses to troubleshoot issues, analyze trends, track site/platform navigation, or gather your demographic information to enhance user experience.

We may use your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy, in our contractual paperwork, or as allowed by applicable laws.

### **4\. Retention of personal information.**

The duration for which we retain information about you depends on the type of information being retained.

We keep your personal data if we have an ongoing legitimate contractual or business need to process your personal information. For example, we may store your name, phone number and email address to contact your about renewing or purchasing subscription to our SEO platform. After such time, we either delete or anonymize your personal data.

If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time.

We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created.

### **5\. How we share information we collect?**

We hire other companies and people to perform a wide variety of services on our behalf. We may need to share your personal data with them to provide information, products and services to you. This includes assisting us with marketing, communication, advertising, fulfillment of contractual obligations, providing support, working on creation and improvement of the functionality and features of our site.

These third parties are authorized only to use your personal data to provide services to us or as required by law.

We may share your information with our parent company, sister concerns, subsidiaries and they may use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may be required by law to disclose your information, and we will try to take steps to limit such disclosure.

If there is a Change of Ownership if we are acquired or otherwise sell our business, we will transfer all of the information to the successor entity. We will try to notify you of any change in ownership or sale by either posting it on our site or by emailing you at the email address we store in our systems.

### **6\. Transfer of information internationally.**

To facilitate our global operations, we may share your personal data internationally in the circumstances defined in the section “How we Share Information we collect”. By using our platform or site, you consent to have your personal data transferred in the United States or any country where Actonia or its service providers, affiliates and subsidiaries maintain facilities.

This Privacy Policy shall apply even if we transfer Personal Information to other countries.

### **7\. Technologies we use.**

Cookies/Flash Cookies: We use cookies, flash cookies and other collected information to improve and further develop and improve our website and platform. We also use cookies to keep your session active and customize your experience. The cookies are stored in your computer. You can delete them or reject them, but if you do, you cannot use our service.

Aggregate Non-Identifiable Information: We use aggregate, non-identifiable information to improve our Website and for other internal and external business purposes.

Server Logs: Our server logs record system information when you view our website or use our platform.

Pixel Tags/Web Beacons: We may embed tracking pixels or web beacons, on our website, in our platform or in emails that we send to you. These allow a web server to read certain data from your browser, check if and when you have viewed an email or web page, track your ip address and the page that was viewed.

### **8\. Access, update and delete your personal data.**

Your personal data belongs to you. At any time, you can contact us at support@seoclarity.net to:

  * Update your personal information.
  * Delete your personal data from our systems.
  * Stop processing your personal data.
  * Data delivery to you or a third party.

If you are a user of our seoClarity platform, request for deletion or to stop processing of your personal data would mean loss of access to our platform.

You may also be receiving marketing emails from us. You can ‘unsubscribe’ or ‘opt-out’ of these communications at any time within the body of the email.

### **9\. Contact our Data Privacy Officer.**

seoClarity has a Data Privacy Officer (DPO), who is responsible for all matters relating to privacy and data protection. The Data Privacy officer can be contacted at the following address:

seoClarity  
Attn: Data Privacy Officer  
2 N. LaSalle St. #1120  
Chicago, IL 60602

Email: privacy@seoclarity.net  
Phone: 771-831-4500

##### _**Last revised 11.18.19**_
